mefeedia.com 2017-12-19

# 

Beachfront Media, LLC, (“MeFeedia”, “we”, or “us’), is committed to protecting your privacy when you use our products and services. The following Privacy Policy was prepared to inform you of the information we collect about you, how that information is used, whether and to whom we disclose it, and the choices you have regarding your personal information. MeFeedia is committed to transparency and accountability in our privacy practices. The following statement describes our Privacy Policy as it relates to the collection, use and disclosure of information we receive from users of our video platform services (“Services”). The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you of the following:

Who we are and the services we provide so that you can understand how our business may impact your privacy,  
What kind of information, including any personally-identifiable information, is collected from you,  
Who collects the information, How the information is used, With whom the information may be shared,  
What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of the information,  
The security procedures that are in place to protect the information; and how you can correct any  
inaccuracies in the information.

It is very important that you read and understand our Privacy Policy. If you do not accept the terms set out in our Privacy Policy, please do not use our product and services. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will advise you that changes have been made by posting a notice on our website or otherwise. Your use of our service constitutes your acceptance of the terms of our Privacy Policy, as may be amended or revised by us, and you are advised to consult our Privacy Policy regularly for any changes (revisions will be reflected by the “last update” notation below). If you have any questions regarding MeFeedia’s policies or practices relating to privacy, please direct them to [privacy@beachfrontmedia.com](mailto:privacy@beachfrontmedia.com).

#### Our Business

**Beachfront Media, LLC has a video platform.** We use our proprietary technology to offer advertising solutions to our clients, which includes working with advertisers to deliver their advertising campaigns across our network of publishers and application (“app”) developers (our “Platform”).  
We offer products and services that help online publishers, agencies, and ad networks manage and deliver online advertising in their videos. We also own websites, and offer technology that allows content providers to place their content into applications. As a consumer, when you see an advertisement before you watch a video, we may help deliver that ad from or for an advertiser to the website or application that has made the video available to you. We also provide a marketplace, where buyers and sellers of online video advertising space can connect and do business.  
We are not in the business of collecting, using, or selling consumer data; however we do offer tools and technologies to advertisers and publishers that allow them to collect and use user data. This is done primarily to enable these buyers and sellers of online video-advertising space to try and ensure that the audience they desire sees their ads and that the advertising itself is delivered and the performance of the advertising can be analyzed. Types of data that may be used for this purpose range from behavioral or interest-related information to geographical or demographic user data. We adhere to the NAI Code of Conduct.

#### Information Collection and How it is Collected

Personally-Identifiable Information.

We do not collect personally-identifiable information in order to help our clients buy, sell, and deliver online video advertising. “Personally-Identifiable Information” means information that alone or when in combination with other information We collect may be used to readily identify, contact, or locate you. There may be some opportunities, for example when you use this Site, where you may choose to enter your name, contact information, and other personal details. For example, if you were interested in becoming one of our clients or using our Services you could provide us with contact details through our Site.

Where we collect personally-identifiable information you will have clear notification of what we are doing so that you can choose not to provide it.

**Non-Personally-Identifiable Information.**

Non-personally-identifiable information is information that, without additional information, cannot be linked to a specific individual by us. We may collect non-personally-identifiable information while you are visiting our Site or the website of one of our advertisers or Web publishers (collectively, “”customers”). For example, while providing the Services to website publishers, advertisers and those working for them, we may collect your IP address, Web pages that you visit, the time and date, and whether or not you clicked on various advertisements (collectively, “Web Surfing Data”).

**Technologies We May Use For Data Collection**

We use different types of technologies to collect non-personally-identifiable information, including cookies, action tags, Web beacons, and single pixel GIFs. Cookies. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes when you request through your browser to receive a particular Web page or content. We use these cookies for three purposes.

Persistent Cookies for Customers Use of Our Site. For our customers who login to our Site so that they may use our Services, we utilize persistent cookies to save your login information for future logins to the Site. This functionality works as it does on many websites that work to enable you to have an easier experience logging in and navigating their websites. We do not use persistent cookies in connection with helping our customers buy, sell, and deliver online video advertising.

Session Cookies to Help Ad Delivery and Accounting. We utilize session ID cookies to enable certain features of the Services, to better understand how you interact with the Services, and to monitor aggregate usage by our users and Web traffic routing on the Services. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you close your browser.

User Data Cookies for Ad Targeting. We utilize cookies to store user data that can aid in targeting of advertisements. This data is usually collected by our Customers and used to deliver advertisements that are more relevant to a user’s interests.

Use of Cookies By Others. Also, the Web publisher or advertiser with whom we partner may use cookies, action tags, GIFs, or Web beacons to collect information when you are visiting their websites. The information they collect is governed by their individual privacy policies, not ours. You are encouraged to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites that you visit. You can learn more about how cookies and related technologies are used in connection with online advertising and analytics by visiting: <http://www.aboutads.info/how-interest-based-ads-work>. 

**Opt-Out Procedure and Cookie Control**

Should you wish to opt-out of us placing a cookie on your browser, you can [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) to deploy an “opt-out” cookie on your browser. This cookie, when installed on your browser, will prevent us from placing a new cookie on that browser and from collecting data on that browser. The NAI’s opt-out tool also allows you to opt-out of the data collection and targeted ad programs of other NAI members. You may access the NAI opt-out [tool here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Our opt-out tool and the NAI opt-out tool, are cookie-based. Both opt-out tools only prevent us from collecting data pertaining to you on the browser on which they are installed, and will only function if your browser is set to accept third-party cookies. If you delete an opt-out cookie from a browser’s cookie files, we may collect data and place a new cookie unless an opt-out cookie is reset on that browser. If you block third-party cookies from being set on your browser, you may not be able to enjoy some features or functionality, and you may see the same content and advertisements repeatedly on some websites.

**Opt-Out Procedure for mobile internet-based or mobile device advertising**

Some of our partners may collect information on mobile internet based sites or mobile devices. Should you wish to opt-out of this type of targeting on both Android and/or IOS platforms please click on the below links:

**Android:**

<https://developer.android.com/google/play-services/id.html#get_started>

Text from the Android Developers Guide is below:

The advertising ID is a unique but user-resettable string identifier that lets ad networks and other apps anonymously identify a user. The user’s advertising ID is made available to apps through APIs provided in Google Play services.

Users can reset their advertising ID at any time, right from the Ads section of the Google Settings app on their devices. From the same app, users can also opt-out of targeted advertising based on the advertising ID by setting the appropriate ad tracking preference. When the user opts-out of targeted ads, this ad tracking preference is made available to apps through a Google Play services API.

Apps making use of the advertising ID must check for and respect the user’s ad tracking preference. Also please note that any use of the advertising ID must abide by the terms of the Google Play Developer Content Policies.

**IOS:**

<http://support.apple.com/kb/HT4228>

Text from Apple’s US privacy policy is below:

Apple and its partners use cookies and other technologies in mobile advertising services to control the number of times you see a given ad, deliver ads that relate to your interests, and measure the effectiveness of ad campaigns. If you do not want to receive ads with this level of relevance on your mobile device, you can opt out by accessing the following link on your device: http://oo.apple.com. Alternatively, if you are using iOS 6 or above operating system on your mobile device, you may opt-out by electing Limit Ad Tracking (Learn More). If you opt out, you will continue to receive the same number of mobile ads, but they may be less relevant because they will not be based on your interests. You may still see ads related to the content on a web page or in an application or based on other non-personal information. Opting out through oo.apple.com applies only to Apple advertising services and does not affect interest-based advertising from other advertising networks. However, if you select Limit Ad Tracking on your mobile device, third party apps are not permitted by contract to use the Advertising Identifier, a non-personal device identifier to serve you targeted ads. 

**Use of Information We Collect**

Use of Non-Personally-Identifiable Information. The non-personally-identifiable data that we and/or our customers collect when using the Services are used for marketing and sales efforts and to better target advertisements to people across the different websites they visit. We may also use the non-personally-identifiable data that it collects to better target content to individuals in an effort to create a personally relevant experience for each person. The non-personally identifiable data is also used to predict responses to advertisements, and to help determine which ads perform best and which content is most appropriate for different individuals.

Use of Personally-Identifiable Information. We use personally-identifiable information we receive primarily to communicate with our customers as we provide the Services. We use information we receive from business customer prospects in the same ways.

Data from Customers. We allow our customers to import data that they have collected or purchased to deliver advertisements to certain audiences through the Services. We are not responsible for and do not control the collection of this data. If you wish to opt out of collection of your information by third parties, then you must do so directly with those third parties.

Sharing and Disclosure of Collected Information

We do not provide personally-identifiable information to our customers or other third parties for their marketing purposes except under the following conditions. If a visitor to our Site provides personally-identifiable information as part of an inquiry about products or services provided by us, we will provide that information only to the proper unit/individual so that they may attempt to respond to the inquiry.

We may share Non-PII collected on our sites via our video advertising platform with unaffiliated third parties for our business purposes. We may also share user level Non-PII and aggregate Non-PII collected via our video advertising platform with unaffiliated third parties for our business purposes, including but not limited to enabling our business partners to help us target ads via the video advertising platform. This information cannot be used to contact or identify any person individually. We may also disclose your information to third parties when obligated to do so by law and in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected, or actual prohibited activities, including but not limited to fraud and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person.

Like most businesses, we will use information we receive for our business purposes and keep this information for as long as we have a legitimate business purpose as permitted by applicable law. We may also disclose your information to third parties when obligated to do so by law and in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected, or actual prohibited activities, including but not limited to fraud and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person.

Service Providers. We may employ third-party companies and individuals to facilitate the Services, to provide the Services on our behalf, to perform website-related services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, Web analytics, and improvement of the Site’s features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Site and Services are used. These third parties have access to your personal information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement. We may disclose information when necessary in cooperation with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or to law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including, but not limited to subpoenas), or to protect our rights, property, or those of others.

Business Transfers. In addition to the above, there is also the possibility that we may one day be purchased by, or merged with, another company or otherwise be reorganized or sold. If that’s the case, the acquiring (or merging) company will have access to your information.

#### Data Retention

The amount of time that we retain data we collect on our systems varies in length based on the type of data collected, but is only retained by us so long as necessary to fulfill our legitimate business needs. Specifically, we retain data as follows:

Personal Information

  * We retain account information obtained from vendors and business partners we work with indefinitely, but reserve the right to delete such information at our convenience. 
  * Any personal information voluntarily provided to us via email communication or through our corporate website is maintained indefinitely until deleted by the corporate email account owner. 

Non-Personally Identifiable Information

  * We retain click-stream data (such as IP address, date/time of visit, browser type, web pages visited, etc.) for up to twelve (12) months. After twelve (12) months, information may be stored in aggregate for statistical and analysis purposes or is deleted. 
  * We retain behavioral segment data for periods as short as thirty (30) days, but may retain some behavioral segment data for up to twelve (12) months. After twelve (12) months, information may be stored in aggregate for statistical analysis purposes or is deleted. 
  * We retain demographic data for periods as short as thirty (30) days, but may retain some demographic data for periods of twelve (12) months. After twelve (12) months information may be stored in aggregate for statistical analysis purposes or is deleted. 

We make efforts to maintain the security of its network and the data we collect. We use various technologies, including, in certain instances, encryption, to ensure security standards. We treat data that is stored on its servers as confidential information. We have an internal security policy with respect to the confidentiality of customer and other data, limiting access only to those employees who we reasonably believe need to know such information for the purpose of performing their jobs. Please keep in mind, however, that the Internet is not a 100% secure medium. Therefore, we use reasonable efforts to protect information, the possibility of somebody defeating its security measures does exist and none of our security measures should be viewed as a guarantee.

#### International Visitors

We are located in the United States of America, and the Site and Services are directed toward persons located within the United States of America. If you are visiting from another region that have laws governing data collection and use please be aware that it may differ from U.S. law, including those whose privacy laws may be more strict than U.S. law, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States to us. If you choose to use our Site and/or Services, you understand and consent to the processing of your personal information in the United States.

#### Links to Web Publishers, Advertisers, and Other Websites

Our Services are combined with content from our customers and other third-party advertisers. Our Services may contain links to other websites. If you choose to visit a Business Customer or other third-party advertiser by clicking on a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third-party link, you will be directed to that third-party’s website. Our provision of a link to a website or a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement of that website or advertisement, nor is it an endorsement of the privacy or information security policies or practices of that website or advertiser. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of Web publishers, advertisers, or other websites that may be linked to our Sites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data, or solicit personal information from you. This Privacy Policy addresses the use and disclosure of information that we collect from you through our Services. Other websites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. You are encouraged to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

#### Accessing Your Personally-Identifiable Information, Making Changes, Or Requesting Deletion

Where we processes personally-identifiable information on our own behalf, you may request access to, correction of, or deletion of personal data held by us. If you desire to access such information we may hold, update the information, or for any privacy or data-protection-related question please write [support@beachfrontmedia.com](mailto:support@beachfrontmedia.com) for assistance. Because we generally process data for others, for any of that data you should make your request directly to the party collecting the information or on whose behalf it has been collected.

#### Security

MeFeedia takes steps to protect the security of information that we collect. To that end, we have designed and deployed hardware, software, and networking solutions in an effort to reasonably secure and protect access to our systems and data. We make efforts to maintain the security of its network and the data we collect. We treat data that is stored on its servers as confidential information. We have an internal security policy with respect to  
the confidentiality of customer and other data, limiting access only to those employees who we reasonably believe need to know such information for the purpose of performing their jobs. Please keep in mind, however, that the Internet is not a 100% secure medium. Therefore, although we use reasonable efforts to protect information, the possibility of somebody defeating its security measures does exist and none of our security measures should be viewed as a guarantee.

#### Children

Neither this Site nor the Service is directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. No sensitive segments or segments are targeted at children. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact us at support@beachfrontmedia.com. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information, we will delete such information from our files.

#### Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits End Users who are California residents to request certain information regarding MeFeedia’s disclosure of personally identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please email [support@beachfrontmedia.com](mailto:support@beachfrontmedia.com). 

#### Notice for Users Outside of the United States

You should be aware that the United States and other countries have not harmonized their privacy regulations. Because the Mefeedia Service is intended specifically for users in the United States, we have written our Privacy Policy to satisfy United States regulations. By using the Mefeedia Service, you agree to the level of privacy protection set out in our Privacy Policy.

#### Changes to Privacy Policy

MeFeedia is committed to continually examining and reviewing its privacy practices, and may make changes to its Privacy Policy. In the event that any changes that we believe are material are made to the company´s privacy practices, we will post a revised Privacy Policy on this website.

This privacy policy was last updated on August 28, 2014.
